Guide to the Dept. of Agricultural Extension Farm Bureau files.
Dept. of Agricultural Extension Farm Bureau files
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dept. of Agricultural Extension Farm Bureau files.
21-24-526
New York State College of Agriculture.Dept. of Agricultural Extension.
4 cubic ft.
Reports, Financial Records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files regarding the New York State Farm Bureau.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files regarding the New York State Farm Bureau.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Agriculture.; Farm Bureau.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Annual Financial Summaries-NYS Agricultural Extension Work 1913-1925 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Annual Financial Summaries-NYS Agricultural Extension Work 1926-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Annual Narrative Reports-NYS Agricultural Extension Service 1912-1927 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Annual Narrative Reports-NYS Agricultural Extension Service 1928-1931 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Annual Narrative Reports-NYS Agricultural Extension Service 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- County Farm Bureau and College Commodity Programs, NYS 1936 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- NYS County Programs 1937 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- County Farm Bureau and College Commodity Programs, NYS 1938 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- County Farm Bureau and College Commodity Programs, NYS 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- County Farm Bureau and College Commodity Programs, NYS Extension Service 1940 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Proceedings of the Eleventh Annual Eastern States Conference on Tuberculosis and Other Animal Diseases; State of NY Department of Agriculture and Markets-Bulletin 242-1930 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- A History of the Extension Service of Iowa State College-Barton Morgan 1934 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Report of the Maryland Agricultural Society-Maryland Farm Bureau Federation-Vol. XIII-1928 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- State of New York Preliminary Report of Joint Committee on Dairy Products, Live Stock and Poultry 1917 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Better Bull Bulletins 1932-1935 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- A Progress Report to the National Resources Board on the Making of a State Plan for New York March 1 to September 1, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- New York State Farm Bureau Monthly (Vol.I, No.1 to Vol.II, No.6) April, 1914- September, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- New York State Farm Bureau News (Vol.II, No.7 to Vol.IV, No.12) October, 1915- December, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- New York State Farm Bureau News (Vol.V, No.1 to Vol.VI, No.12) January, 1917- December, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Extension Service News (Farm Bureau News), (Vol.II, No.1 to Vol.III, No.12) January, 1919- December, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- County Farm Bureau and College Commodity Programs-NYS Extension Service 1941 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- County Farm Bureau Programs NYS 1931 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- County Farm Bureau Programs Supplement to 1941 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- County Farm Bureau Programs-NYS Extension Service 1942 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Service Letters 1935 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Service Letters-NYS Extension Service 1936 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Service Letters-NYS Extension Service 1937 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Service Letters-NYS Extension Service 1939 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Service Letters-NYS Extension Service 1940 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Service Letters-NYS Extension Service 1941 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Service Letters-NYS Extension Service 1942 (Box 4, Folder 11)